Where's Snoopy?
Snoopy, Come Home is a family, animation film directed by Bill Melendez.
When Snoopy receives a letter from his original owner Lila, he goes to visit her in the
hospital while Charlie Brown and the gang are on the lookout for him.
Suddenly, Snoopy feels that he must go live with Lila,
but must say goodbye to all his friends.
In his adventure to the hospital, he encounters numerous "No Dogs Allowed"
signs, an annoying little girl who desires to keep him, and more!
Charlie Brown (voice), played by Chad Webber.
Snoopy / Woodstock (voice), played by Bill Melendez.
Lucy Van Pelt (voice), played by Robin Kohn.
Linus Van Pelt (voice), played by Stephen Shea.
Schroeder (voice), played by David Carey.
Sally Brown (voice), played by Hilary Momberger-Powers.
Snoopy Come Home is a 1972 American animated musical comedy-drama film
directed by Bill Melendez and written by Charles M.
Schulz, based on the Peanuts comic strip.
Marking the on-screen debut of Woodstock, who had first appeared in the strip in 1967, the main plot was based on a storyline
from August 1968 (which was the only Cinema Center Films production to feature the Peanuts character Woodstock).
The only Peanuts film during composer Vince Guaraldi’s lifetime without a score composed by him, its music was composed by the Sherman Brothers, who
composed the music for various Disney films like Mary Poppins (1964), The Jungle Book (1967), and Bedknobs and Broomsticks (1971).
Snoopy Come Home was released on August 9, 1972, by National General Corporation, produced by Lee Mendelson
Films, Bill Melendez Productions and Cinema Center Films (in the latter's final production).
Despite only grossing less than a quarter of its $1 million dollar budget commercially, it received
overwhelmingly positive reviews from critics and fared much more successfully on home video.
The film explores themes of cartoon, tearjerker, beagle.
The tone is emotional.